Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
THE APARTMENT JOB
There's going to be a bus stop
about 300 meters in front of you.
Do you see it?
Yes. I see it.
Crash into the woman
standing there!
Please help my sister.
What do you mean?
My sister
is Kang Ha-jeong.
Kang Ha-jeong? The accounting manager?
I think…
she did something she shouldn't have.
What do you mean?
She has a ledger.
A ledger recording how
the apartment funds were embezzled.
Kang Ha-jeong. the accounting manager.
is Kang Ha-ri's sister.
What?
And she has the actual ledger recording
how the reserve fund was embezzled.
The ledger?
The actual ledger?
Wasn't she working for Lee Chung-won?
Lee Chung-won
doesn't seem to know about it either.
Ms. Kang probably made it
to protect herself.
Boss. doesn't this mean we have
-a weapon against him now?
-Right.
Only if we get our hands on it.
You guys keep an eye
on Kang Ha-jeong for now.
-Yes. sir.
This could be a matter
of life and death for us.
I'm telling you. I can't do this.
I'm going to pretend I didn't hear this.
She sat in the third row
from the back of the 125 bus.
Yes. she's entering her house.
What is it? Did you get caught?
No. it's nothing.
Ten billion for just driving?
Boss. he's definitely planning
to take someone out.
You can't do this. Boss.
Boss. I'll do it instead.
I've been the youngest for years.
I have to be a better driver than you.
The "hangnail" Lee Chung-won mentioned
must be Kang Ha-jeong.
Will he stop if I refuse. though?
He'll just get someone
desperate for money to do it instead.
I need to take the wheel
to get a chance to save Ms. Kang.
Ms. Kang. are you okay?
We're here to help.
This is ten billion won.
I told you I'd give you the money
once you did this.
You can save your old boss
with this money.
You shouldn't leave him there
when he's already sick.
All you had to do
was crash into a woman
standing right there.
You've pulled off harder things than that.
but you fail to do the easiest job?
I may be a bad guy.
but you're just trash.
Trash?
You're being quite rude to a guy
who's interested in you.
I don't date trash.
Then what will you do with me?
I have an item that will interest you.
A ledger of all the trashy things
a construction company president did
to embezzle the reserve fund
of an apartment complex
that he built himself.
Then what about this?
Let's exchange the ledger
for Park Yong-man.
You needed that ten billion
to get Park Yong-man released.
So…
COMMISSIONER KWAK JU-GWON
Yes. Mr. Lee.
What prompts this late-night call?
Commissioner. I have a favor to ask you.
Let's get ready
to release Park Yong-man on medical bail.
What? Park Yong-man?
The boss of Park Hae-kang.
the guy you've been using.
I'll let you join the One Club.
so get ready to release Park Yong-man.
All right. I'll get it ready.
If you want him released.
bring me the ledger.
Simple. isn't it?
My sister really isn't a bad person.
I swear.
They say it's pancreatic cancer.
He has about three months left.
I searched everywhere.
but the ledger isn't here.
It seems she's already moved it.
It's not there?
Then that means
it's no longer just a document.
It's a weapon now.
I'm sorry. sir. I'll track her again.
She can't hide forever.
Good work. Mr. Kim.
He really is competent.
But if he keeps being unpredictable.
it's going to be a problem.
If I turn my back on him…
he won't be able to handle it.
THE APARTMENT JOB
Ha-jeong!
Ha-jeong. are you okay? Are you hurt?
I can't believe this!
Tell me.
What bastard was trying to kill you?
Tell me. You must know who it is!
Who is it? Who did this to my sister?
Where's the ledger?
You almost got killed because of it.
I hid the ledger.
She doesn't know where it is.
Give me the ledger.
It's not something you can handle.
And why would you need to take
something that dangerous?
I need it
to at least try to make a deal.
A deal?
With who?
The person who tried to kill my sister?
Who is it?
The former president?
Or the facility manager?
Who is it?
If they want to kill my sister over it.
then that means the ledger
is their weakness.
So why should I hand it over to you?
Mr. Park.
That ledger is also
a record of my sister's crimes.
I can't just hand it over.
The person after her life
isn't someone you can handle.
You're not even telling me
who this person is.
How can I trust you with the ledger?
That ledger is my sister's lifeline.
Her life depends on it right now.
I can't hand it over.
So you mean
the accounting manager
is Kang Ha-ri's sister?
That means she's working
with the penthouse guy.
How did our enemy end up
sitting right in the middle
of our living room?
Hang on. It's going to be tough
having to make meals
for Ms. Kang and her sister too.
There's another mouth to feed now.
Well. this is an emergency.
We just have to set the table
for one more person. right?
Fine. You don't have to be so serious.
I hope she's not a glutton
like somebody here.
Where are you going. Gyeong-buk?
Here.
Kang Ha-ri said
sweets are the best for stress.
CHOCOLATE MILK
Thanks.
So she likes chocolate.
Shameless.
She does seem to like food.
We got the security cam footage
near Kang Ha-jeong's last known location.
She was last seen entering
True Value's Building 114.
Building 114?
That's where Park Hae-kang lives.
Yes. sir.
We assume she's in his house.
What? Are they dating?
Kang Ha-jeong has a little sister
named Kang Ha-ri.
She's Park Hae-kang's wife.
What's going on here?
So they're in-laws?
It's actually more complicated.
Park Hae-kang and Kang Ha-ri
aren't registered as spouses.
His so-called brothers
are men from his gambling den.
and his father is actually
a wanted gambler.
His entire family is fake.
What?
Wow. You've got to be kidding me.
How ridiculous.
What about his wife?
She was hired through a stand-in service
to play the role of his bride.
So this whole thing was just
a business arrangement between them?
Just a business arrangement.
That means they'll come
wagging their tails
at the smell of money.
How easy.
I hid the ledger in a safe spot.
No one will be able to find it.
I'm sorry.
I didn't expect things to get this bad.
Who is it?
Who ordered you to embezzle the fund?
It was me.
I made the choice.
Nobody ordered me to do it.
So it's me.
I'm the one who ordered it.
You needed the money to support me.
Ha-ri.
I was so scared
that something would happen to you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Ha-ri.
Why won't she give it to you
when things have gotten so bad?
I really didn't expect her to be so cold.
It's understandable.
Her sister's life is on the line.
She won't just hand it over.
Hey. whose side are you on?
Whose side? We're all family here.
Don't be stupid. Boss.
What do we do now?
Ms. Kang is right.
Asking her for the ledger
is the same as sacrificing
Kang Ha-jeong for our sake.
Then what about Yong-man?
Without the ledger. how would we--
That's why we're going with Plan B.
We're going after Lee Chung-won
without the ledger.
Lee Chung-won?
Boss. we'd be fighting against Taesan.
We don't even have
any leverage against them.
I'll make that myself.
But have you guys heard of the One Club?
One Club?
No. I've never been there.
The one in Hongdae?
I'll let you join the One Club.
so get ready to release Park Yong-man.
The commissioner was behind
Chief Son Dae-un.
The commissioner needed ten billion won
to join this "One Club."
and that's why
Mr. Son demanded it from us.
What?
What kind of big shots
are in this One Club
that you need ten billion to join?
Right?
It seems like
Lee Chung-won is managing that club.
Let's dig into what kind of people
are in this One Club
and what Lee Chung-won is trying
to pull there.
Yes. Boss.
She's not picking up?
No. Her phone's off.
She's not the type to skip work like this.
I wonder what's going on.
Let's focus on work for now.
I'm sure she'll call.
Try calling her again.
-Should I?
-Yes.
Ha-jeong. are you all right?
Say something.
You're scaring me.
Good morning. everyone!
-Hello.
-Good morning.
What brings you here so early?
This is my workplace.
Of course. I should be here.
-Isn't that right?
-Yes. of course.
Mr. Choi.
Please call a meeting
with the tenant representatives.
What? The tenant representatives?
Why do you need…
I'm the president.
I can't sit back and do nothing.
It's my duty to work for this apartment.
Please call a tenants' representative
meeting immediately.
Mom. your eyes are red.
Did you have a fight with your sister?
No. we just stayed up late chatting.
She looked like
she had a nightmare. though.
I wish Ha-jeong would keep
staying with us.
Why?
Uncle Hae-kang
and my dad will protect her.
Then she won't be scared anymore.
But Mom.
There's a worm
growing in our kindergarten wall.
It keeps getting longer.
I'm scared it'll turn into a snake.
A worm is getting longer?
My teacher told me it's a secret.
So don't tell anyone about it.
-Hello.
-Good morning.
-See you later. Gyeong-buk.
-Okay.
-Bye.
Bye.
-Hello.
Would you like to join us for coffee?
Coffee?
You know Su-a. who transferred
to the Harvard Class yesterday?
I met her mom.
and she said
Su-a got a rash all over her body
as soon as she started
going to kindergarten.
She asked if Seo-jun was okay.
Ru-i actually developed eczema
while attending kindergarten too.
but we couldn't be sure
it was because of that.
You know how we'd suspected
they had used cheap materials?
-Yeah.
-Right.
And Hye-jun told me
she used an umbrella in class yesterday.
so I first thought
they were just having fun.
But she said water fell from the ceiling.
Goodness.
Min-jun said it was raining in class too.
What if it really was shoddy construction?
There's a worm
growing in our kindergarten wall.
It keeps getting longer.
We filed a complaint
with the Office of Education.
-but they said it's fine.
-Right.
A private inspection company came
and checked everything.
They said it's safe.
Well. it's the law.
What else can we do anyway?
It's not the law.
The method was wrong.
Don't trust the kindergarten.
File an information disclosure request.
We should compare each item
on the diagnostic report.
We can view the report?
It's our right as citizens.
This should be reported
as a public interest violation.
Children's safety
is a matter of public interest.
If we report this
to the Civil Rights Commission.
the officials will have to act.
You're so smart. Ms. Kang.
How do you know stuff like that?
I just know a tiny bit.
Then you can come with us
to the Office of Education.
She's right.
-That's a great idea.
-Yes.
Me?
-Let's go together.
-Right.
-Let's go!
I'm so glad.
Why did I have to say that?
I'm not even a lawyer.
You should stop meddling
in other people's lives.
Just worry about yourself and Ha-jeong.
President Park's wife?
Yes. that's me.
Who…
I'm just curious how much you know
about your husband.
Should I call you Kang Ha-jeong's sister?
UNDER REPAIR
WILL BE COMPLETED SOON
Here. Kang Ha-ri.
Your sister did something quite bold.
So it's you.
You tried to kill my sister.
You're quick-witted.
You're right. That was me.
You bastard.
You're smart. but you're naive.
Am I the only bad guy here?
Is your sister a good person. then?
Your sister teamed up with a bad guy
and helped him cover up his crimes.
How about 500 million?
Your sister's severance pay and bonus.
But I want that ledger in return.
Why not?
I'm sure that's more than what you got
for playing Park Hae-kang's wife.
The pay is better.
but the benefits aren't that great.
How can I trust a boss
who tried to kill someone
who worked for him?
So you're the type to hold grudges.
Forget it.
If you touch my sister again.
I'll make you realize you messed
with the wrong person.
Your sister is staying
at Park Hae-kang's. right?
Do you really think Park Hae-kang
will protect you two until the end?
At least he doesn't
stab people in the back.
You really have no clue. do you?
Park Hae-kang actually came here
to take the 17 billion won
in the reserve fund.
He can only take the fund
if he's the president.
He's been using you.
Do you still not get it?
Gyeong-buk.
Hang on.
Candied sweet potatoes.
Are you dreaming?
Move.
You were right.
I was bored just sitting around.
There were some sweet potatoes.
so I made a snack for Gyeong-buk.
I made plenty. so have some.
I didn't know you had such talent.
Come and have some. They're tasty.
Your gaze
is sweeter
than the candied sweet potatoes.
Come and try this.
-Come on.
-Come here.
Try some.
-Enjoy.
-Thank you.
You're welcome.
Mr. Park.
Where's Park Hae-kang?
Come out here!
Ha-ri. what's wrong?
What?
-What is it?
-Is it true?
Is what true?
The reason why you were
desperate to become the president.
Was it all
because of the 17 billion
in the reserve fund?
Did you meet Lee Chung-won?
Yes.
I could tell when I met him.
That man is openly evil.
but you're a real fraud
who pretends to be a good guy
-while stabbing people in the back.
-Ms. Kang.
You're being too harsh…
So?
Do you feel betrayed because I'm a fraud?
Ms. Kang.
stop pretending like you're a victim.
What?
You pretended to be my wife
because you needed money too.
Method acting?
Paid labor?
Don't be silly.
You chose to be part of a fake family
because of money.
You're right.
I did this for the money.
But at the very least.
I never betrayed people's trust
while pretending to be righteous.
I thought you were sincerely
trying to make this a better place.
I just feel
so embarrassed
that I took your side because of that.
Ha-jeong.
Let's go. I can't stay here any longer.
What will you do once you leave?
Why do you think
Lee Chung-won met with you?
This means
he knows where Ha-jeong is.
Let's talk inside for a moment.
Park Hae-kang
saved me when I almost died.
I know that.
but he's also the one
who planned all this to take the fund.
You did this because of money too.
Why do you expect him to be innocent?
He saved me when he knew
that 17 billion was already gone.
You keeping the ledger hidden
isn't helping him in any way.
but look.
He's putting himself at risk
by protecting us.
You may be used to
being called a fraud and a thug
by other people.
but it must be the first time
hearing it from someone who trusted you.
That's why you have
that look on your face.
What look?
You look like you got caught being human
despite being a fraud.
Let's begin True Value State's first
tenants' representative council meeting.
Welcome. everyone.
We did name this
a tenants' council meeting.
but our real goal
is for everyone to get along here.
regardless of whether
the unit is a rental or owner-occupied.
Everything you say is absolutely right.
Do you have any ideas. President Jang?
I would like
to suggest a safety patrol.
But President Jang.
we already have guards…
Before arguing about
who the true owners of True Value are.
we should show everyone
that we're the ones
who care the most about this place.
So.
starting tonight.
who wants to join me
in patrolling the complex?
Right. Thank you.
I knew it.
We elected such good representatives.
Cats never come this way.
They always stay over there.
Gosh. Look.
The light's off.
The trail in front of Building 107.
-Write that down.
-Okay.
Okay.
Shall we go that way?
Excuse me.
-Where do you live?
-Building 109.
This building?
We're True Value's safety patrol.
The building reps are working hard
for this apartment complex.
-This building?
-Yes.
-You shouldn't stay out too late.
-Okay.
-It's a dangerous world.
-Right.
You can't see me.
No. you hold it.
Stretch your arm out. okay?
Kids!
What are you doing?
It's late. you know.
Hyeong-u. don't you live in Building 105?
Yes. Hello.
Your mom will be waiting. Go home.
How many girlfriends do you have?
Gosh!
I'll call you!
-Don't.
-Okay.
Stop making your mom worry!
Everyone knows
he gives his mom a hard time.
He's too handsome for his own good.
Great work today. everyone.
-Thank you.
-I'll see you tomorrow.
-All right.
I'm going to take a detour back home.
-Okay.
-Bye.
TRUE VALUE KINDERGARTEN
What is that?
What is all this?
Goodness.
It's going to crumble down soon.
My gosh.
You scared me.
What are you doing?
Why do I feel so thirsty?
Do you remember
how you said it feels
like you have to repay your sister?
What about it?
I told you I have someone like that too.
So?
That person
is in jail right now.
And he's innocent.
For people like me.
there are only two ways
to get involved with the police.
Greasing their palms
and coexisting with them.
or getting hauled in as a suspect.
I did the former.
I was one of their favorite cash cows.
But the ones who thought of me
as a goose laying golden eggs
took my old boss to cut me open.
And they told me to bring ten billion
if I wanted to get him released.
That's when I found out
there was money in this apartment complex.
I did all this
because of the reserve fund.
It's true I became the president
with ill intentions.
And it's true that I dragged you into this
when you had no clue.
I just thought it would be better
for you not to know.
but I guess
I've only deceived you.
I apologize.
I'm sorry.
So what will you do now?
There's no money in the account.
and I won't give you the ledger.
I'll find another way.
Even so.
I promise to keep the two of you safe.
I promise.
Have it with a poached egg.
This isn't cheese?
All right.
Here. Enjoy.
Asparagus?
Gyeong-buk.
Tell Ha-ri to eat.
Ha-ri. Uncle Hae-kang said you should eat.
Gyeong-buk. tell your uncle
that I don't have an appetite.
She doesn't have an appetite?
She'll have no energy all day
if she skips breakfast.
Tell her to at least have a bite.
Tell him to stay out of my business
and enjoy his own meal.
My teacher said
fighting is bad.
and not making up after that
is even worse.
You're awful.
Gyeong-buk. we're not fighting--
Just make up.
If you don't.
I'm not going to kindergarten today.
I'm not eating. either!
-Good job. Gyeong-buk!
-Nice!
Gyeong-buk's angry.
Fine. let's make up.
Okay. Let's make up.
Gyeong-buk. we made up.
-We made up.
Now hug each other.
-What?
My teacher said you have to hug
when you apologize.
No. there's no need.
Gyeong-buk's teacher is very wise.
Come on. We should apologize too.
Let's make up.
-We should apologize.
-What?
-What…
-Let's make up.
No. it's fine.
Let's go.
-I said it's fine!
-They need to hug?
What are you doing?
Okay. fine. Let's make up.
We're making up.
-Let's make up.
-Bigger hug!
TRUE VALUE KINDERGARTEN
ENROLLMENT OPEN
What do I do?
If I expose this.
I'll become a traitor to True Value.
Bye!
Mom!
Gosh. This is giving me a headache.
Oh dear.
Construction will officially start
next month.
I wanted you to see the empty plot
before that.
Everything here will change completely.
You should see this place one last time.
I hope you'll care about the project
as it takes shape
and show lots of support.
You know my son-in-law's
law firm represents
the top legal figures in Korea. right?
Yes.
So proceed with the project
without worrying about legal issues.
Speed is the most important.
The relic incident slowed things down.
Let's speed things up.
Of course. I'll have everything
moving so fast. it'll be hard to keep up.
We're going to start releasing articles.
I'll get the prices up.
The VIP is keeping an eye on this as well.
Oman New Town is emerging
as a potential solution
to the housing shortage in Seoul!
We'll provide
all the policy support you need.
Thank you.
Thank you. everyone!
OMAN NEW TOWN
GEOLOGICAL SURVEY
Let's zoom in.
I can even see their pores.
This camera is amazing.
Can you tell who they are?
That guy…
I saw him on the news.
Who was he again?
He's always with the president.
The Senior Secretary for Civil Affairs.
And the president of Gongyeong Daily.
They're all gathered
to fill their pockets.
My fingers are trembling.
Get their faces clearly.
These will be their memorial photos.
You're not allowed to take photos here.
-Sorry about that.
-Move your equipment.
We had to conduct a geological survey.
We're just here to do our job. Look!
We're heading out.
We'll wrap up now!
We're almost done.
ONE CLUB
Look. Boss.
Construction. law.
politics.
media.
Korea's most powerful figures
are all gathered here.
Can you recognize this man?
The Senior Secretary for Civil Affairs.
The official right below the president.
And next to him
is the Supreme Court Justice.
And in the back
are the president of Gongyeong Daily
and the Prosecutor General.
They're the members of the One Club.
No wonder he wasn't scared of anything.
He was using
the entire country as his shield.
I didn't order any food.
Ms. Kang.
What is it? I was sleeping…
Look at this.
What is this?
That's Gyeong-buk's kindergarten.
That's what the exterior wall
looks like right now.
But we can see the rebar.
Couldn't the building
collapse at any moment?
The kindergarten mothers
suspected shoddy construction too.
I've been so torn about what to do.
If I expose this issue.
the apartment prices will drop for sure.
and they'll attack the rental units again.
saying we don't care if the prices drop.
Still. this isn't a trivial matter.
President Park.
I think you should step up
and handle this.
All right.
This involves the safety of the kids here.
Of course.
I should step up as the president.
TRUE VALUE KINDERGARTEN
Wait just a moment.
Are you filming a prison escape movie?
Papillon really ruined all you kids.
Are you filming a spy movie or what?
Tom Cruise really ruined all you kids.
This isn't mine.
That's mine.
Everyone. move aside.
Let me smash it in.
Get a grip!
It'll cost the residents money
to get it fixed if you break it.
Ma Dong-seok ruined all you kids.
Step back!
Move aside.
Security has been disabled.
You had a key?
-You should've told us.
-I told you.
He's got main character syndrome.
All right. Gosh.
Check thoroughly.
Cracks in the wall and stuff.
Check if there's anything off.
We'll check thoroughly.
You idiot. Are you stealing kids' candy?
Are you here to stuff your face?
Worm.
Right. The worm.
What's that?
Are you crying?
No…
It's leaking.
Oh my gosh.
It wasn't just one crack.
Is this the spot you were talking about?
Pull it back.
You shouldn't see this. Mr. Kim.
-Why?
-Hey.
-Stay calm.
-Let go.
What is this?
The mothers filed a complaint.
so an inspection company came.
but they said it was safe.
What part of this is safe?
This is practically attempted murder.
I can't believe these assholes.
I guess Taesan really is powerful.
How could they even
think about covering this up?
That's why we need to figure out
what to do about this.
What should we do. President Park?
No. Never.
You can't go to kindergarten today.
Why not?
Well. the kindergarten…
-Just don't go.
-I…
I also want you
to skip kindergarten today.
Then who will I play with?
We can all play with you.
Why are you looking at me?
Do you not care about the other kids?
It's fine as long as your kid is safe?
Turning a blind eye
makes you equally guilty. Mr. Park.
All right. I'll let you
play at a kids cafe today.
And bring all your friends!
You're the best!
Why is he so excited?
What's a kids cafe?
It's like an indoor playground for kids
and a battleground for parents.
Wait!
I'm afraid of heights.
Why isn't it falling?
Call the manager!
Why do you need the manager?
I got it!
Good job!
Bathroom! Where's the bathroom?
I'm so exhausted.
How are they so full of energy?
Delivering packages was easier than this.
Do you have pain relief patches?
This counts as a workplace injury.
Why do we keep spending money
when we're here to take it?
Let's just leave. please.
Just think of this as an investment.
Boss!
There's no movement. sir.
Park Hae-kang isn't doing anything?
No. sir.
He's just walking
around the apartment complex
and living quietly.
He doesn't hate money.
and he wouldn't just sit and watch
as his old boss dies.
What's he up to?
Mr. Kim.
Did I overestimate Park Hae-kang?
Should I keep watching him. sir?
He'll have no choice but to come to me.
That ledger will become useless
if Park Yong-man dies.
You can go.
Yes. sir.
Even if you keep holding out
until the end.
all that will be left
is this single photo.
You're such a fool.
Park Hae-kang.
I called for an urgent meeting today
because something is happening
in True Value State
that I simply cannot turn a blind eye to.
President Jang.
CONSTRUCTION DEFECTS
What is that?
What's that?
Are those photos real?
Is this why
the kindergarten was shut down?
These are photos
from True Value's kindergarten.
As you can see.
this goes beyond a minor defect.
I had the kindergarten shut down
as the president.
Hold on.
Has the building really aged this fast?
No.
this is clearly a sign
of shoddy construction.
-Shoddy construction?
Do you know how serious an issue this is?
This could make our property values
plummet overnight.
That's not the problem!
Don't you see the cracks in the photos?
I trusted the director
and thought it was safe.
The inspection company
stated that the kindergarten was safe
because it was a subsidiary
of Taesan Construction.
So they were putting our children
in danger the whole time?
You're making a fuss
over something that hasn't happened yet.
The president is being overly worried.
calling it shoddy construction.
Let's not cause a commotion.
This concerns the safety of our children.
We must explain the situation
to the residents
and make it public--
Wait. Make it public?
Can't we just get things repaired quietly?
Repairs won't fix everything.
We should file a complaint and demand
action from Taesan Construction.
We can't send our kids back there.
Then send them
to a different kindergarten.
There are dozens of kindergartens
in our neighborhood.
Right. Send them somewhere else.
Imagine what will happen if rumors spread.
Look. I got the chills
just thinking about it.
I'm more scared about that.
You should think
about the residents' assets.
Their houses are everything to them.
In any case.
this can never be made public.
A president dropping apartment prices?
Whose side are you even on?
You should just step down!
Yes. step down.
Step down!
Everyone. listen.
You can't trade
our children's safety for money.
And if an accident occurs
at the kindergarten.
what would you do then?
-You're just a tenant!
The homeowners are speaking.
You don't care
because it's not your own house.
Property prices are a serious matter
directly tied to our livelihoods.
Fine. I get it.
Continue the meeting. President Park.
Unbelievable.
Just a moment.
Who among you
doesn't have any children?
Raise your hands.
All right. then.
I will do my job as president.
PRESIDENT PARK HAE-KANG
Yes?
What are you going to do?
What will you do
about the defective construction?
Are you going to drop it
just because they're opposing it?
We should make a formal complaint…
No. wait. Let's report this to the media.
Lee Chung-won has control
over the media as well.
So you're just going to sit back
and do nothing?
If we can't use the media.
we can become the media instead.
Ms. Kang is here too.
Perfect timing. everyone.
What?
We came to tell you
we won't just transfer kindergartens.
This isn't just
a minor construction mistake.
They put our children's lives
at risk for money.
We should ring the bell for society.
You mean "sound the alarm."
Right.
Can you think of any ideas.
President Park?
It's right here.
Me?
Why?
DAMN IN-LAWS
Damn in-laws.
Mother. only factories would make
300 batches of kimchi.
That's why I got…
You're shaking like crazy!
You don't even have in-laws.
Why are you watching that?
-Don't you know her?
-I don't.
She's really popular.
-Who is it?
-"Damn in-laws!"
-She has over a million subscribers.
-Damn in-laws!
That voice sounds familiar.
"Damn in-laws"?
Oh no. You caught me.
This isn't going to be an exposé video.
It's going to be a marketing video
for a luxury kindergarten.
So keep the tone as luxurious
as you can. okay?
Ms. Kang. begin when I give the sign.
Don't worry.
All right. Are you all ready?
Let's go.
Go on.
Everyone. Taesan Construction
has introduced a special system
to improve children's balance.
An automatic floor-tilting system.
When you place an apple on a table…
As you can see.
they've installed this to help children
build lower-body strength.
Oh my. It seems like Taesan Construction
wants to turn our kids
into future gymnastics champions.
Oh. that's cold!
You must be worried about
your children's skin in the dry winter.
But here. there's a mist of cement dust
operating 24 hours a day.
The damp atmosphere
gives off a high-end basement vibe.
You could film Parasite here!
How damp!
Look at these luxurious drops of water
falling from the ceiling.
Taesan Construction staff.
would you like to come here
in person for a shower?
Oh. that's cold!
No way!
And here's the highlight.
Shall we see what they've hidden
behind this pretty facade
saying "Enrollment Open"?
Mothers. please reveal it!
This is nuts.
It seems they've made art
instead of a building.
This premium crack pattern
is quite unique. isn't it?
That's truly a magnificent crack.
Subscribers.
wouldn't it be a waste
to keep such a place to ourselves?
So we'll share this secret with you all.
Shoddy construction. zero conscience.
The company name is…
-Tae.
-San.
-Con.
-Struction.
No way!
Damn in-laws.
I might put up with in-laws.
but I won't put up with anyone
harming our kids!
Listen up. Taesan Construction.
We're getting back every penny
you skimmed from the rebar costs.
so go ahead
and try holding out until the end.
Taesan Construction may silence the media.
but they can't silence
my channel's subscribers.
Should I upload the video now?
Instead of fighting your in-laws.
let's take on the construction company
for our children this time.
All right. let's do this.
Boss. look at the view count going up.
It's insane.
Why didn't I know that Seo-jun's mom
was "Damn In-Laws"?
I'm a subscriber.
"Is their headquarters
built out of Styrofoam?"
"Taesan loves shoddy construction."
The comments are blowing up.
They were fools
to mess with Korean mothers.
They may silence the media.
but they can't silence the mothers.
Right.
Taesan Construction
should be responding soon.
Of course.
We're contacting influencers
who are spreading the video
and asking them to delete it.
Most of them did
when we offered money. but…
"But"?
There are posts on
the True Value mothers' online community
requesting an explanation from Taesan
and a full safety inspection
of the apartment complex.
What the hell is the legal team doing?
Mothers' community or not.
just sue everyone.
Make sure everyone who spreads the video
will want to cut off their own hands.
Yes. sir.
SENIOR SECRETARY SONG U-SIK
What about the old geezers?
The Prosecutor General
seems to be contacting
other construction company presidents.
What?
How dare he?
It seems like he's trying to find
a company to keep Taesan in check.
Keep Taesan in check?
Who do they think they are
to keep me in check?
They're all just sitting around
waiting for me to bring them money.
GONGYEONG DAILY LEE SANG-GYU
These old geezers are all panicking.
worried this will affect
the Oman New Town project.
Park Hae-kang…
Park Hae-kang!
I loved his competence.
but now that he's my enemy.
I want to kill him.
Not a single person is passing by.
Why do we have to sit out here
in the freezing cold?
The boss told us to make sure
nobody goes inside.
They'll come to get rid of the evidence.
I put up thermal sensors
all around the entrance.
The alarm will go off
even if an ant walks by.
But don't the Taesan guys sleep at all?
They'd have to be paid
for night shifts too.
Don't be stupid.
Would thieves even care about labor laws?
Geez.
Intruder alert!
Cover me!
Damn it.
Is this a secret weapon sent by Taesan?
Sorry. that's the snack I was eating.
Just pick one. Doze off or eat.
Intruder alert canceled.
Good job. Stick to the manual.
Manual. my foot…
This is so satisfying.
We need to have japchae to celebrate.
Boss. look at this.
Our community forum
is blowing up right now.
Lee Chung-won's going
to feel pressured for sure.
Right.
He still pisses me off. though.
How dare he?
If he lays a finger on our old boss.
I'm going to tear
the whole Oman New Town apart.
You shouldn't slice the carrots like that!
This is for the japchae.
The sizes are all different.
Is this for Gyeong-buk?
Why are you cutting them
into whale shapes?
Je-gil. you should be helping me out here.
You're just staring at that forum.
I should just destroy that laptop.
-Look at him.
-Wait. Boss.
I think you should see this.
Mr. Park.
That post on the forum…
What's going on?
EXPOSING PARK HAE-KANG'S CORRUPTION
I'm the facility manager
of True Value State.
Choi Yeong-jae.
Today.
I am staking
my lifelong professional integrity
on the truth I'm about to reveal.
The 17.8 billion won
in the long-term repair reserve fund
that all the residents
gathered over the past years…
was embezzled by President Park Hae-kang
and the accounting manager. Kang Ha-jeong.
as part
of an organized scheme.
I am ashamed to admit
that as the facility manager.
I was deceived and used by them.
blinded by their elaborate collusion
and falsified documents.
What kind of bullshit is this?
It's late.
but I found the courage to confess
in order to prevent any further harm.
President Park embezzled the reserve fund.
Goodness.
What? Embezzled?
Oh my goodness.
They embezzled how much?
It's 17.8 billion won!
No way! 17.8 billion?
They embezzled 17.8 billion?
This doesn't even compare
to President Seo.
I promise to cooperate
with any investigations.
You still can't reach Mr. Choi?
The number you've dialed…
His phone's turned off.
Should we just unplug all the phones?
Lastly.
I sincerely apologize to all the residents
of True Value.
I can't believe this.
He's claiming that Mr. Park
and Ha-jeong took the 17.8 billion?
Why is this happening?
This is ridiculous.
Mr. Choi is stabbing us in the back
when he's the one who took the money.
Boss.
What do we do?
-Boss!
-What should we do?
Who is it this time?
Tell them to come back later.
Police! Open the door.
-Pol…
-Police?
How did they come so quickly?
I'll go and buy some time.
-No. wait!
-Why?
Don't open the door just yet.
What do we do now. Mr. Park?
Lizard. Ha-jeong. get inside.
You guys hide too.
-Ms. Kang. come on.
-Hurry up!
What are we supposed to do?
-Hurry up.
-Go inside.
Sangwon Police Major Crimes Unit.
Mr. Park Hae-kang?
You're under arrest
for embezzlement and breach of trust.
Due to the risk of flight.
we're arresting you without a warrant.
You have the right to retain an attorney.
to present your defense.
and to remain silent.
Anything you say can
and will be used against you--
Let's go.
Boss!
Let go!
-Don't touch the officer.
-Step back!
-Hey.
-Wait!
You should explain what's going on!
Boss.
The facility manager was lying!
-Boss.
Mr. Park.
THE APARTMENT JOB
How can this be the face of someone
who took 17.8 billion won?
Let me talk to you. Mr. Choi.
What's with you?
Get him!
I'm actually curious.
Did you really think
exposing that shoddy construction
would achieve some great justice?
Your photos look great.
We should be sticking together.
Stick together and do what?
We have to stay right here. as a family.
You thief!
I won't run away
until we catch the one
who took the 17.8 billion.
It was my oversight.
We will rebuild it
into one of the finest kindergartens.
President Lee Chung-won.
Are you going to demolish all 9.800
apartments here and rebuild them again?
He's really blowing everything up.
Subtitle translation by: Juyoung Park
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org